<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdf:RDF
	xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
	xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#"
	xmlns:owl="http://www.w3.org/2002/07/owl#"
	xmlns:dct="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
	xmlns:dbo="http://dbpedia.org/ontology/"
	xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:prov="http://www.w3.org/ns/prov#"
	xmlns:ns8="http://dbpedia.org/ontology/PopulatedPlace/"
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss/"
	xmlns:dbp="http://dbpedia.org/property/"
	xmlns:ns11="http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/" >
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://dbpedia.org/resource/London">
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/ontology/Location" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/ontology/Place" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/ontology/PopulatedPlace" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Municipality108626283" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Location100027167" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Town108665504" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://www.w3.org/2002/07/owl#Thing" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/WikicatStaplePorts" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Center108523483" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Capital108518505" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Point108620061" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/City108524735" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://umbel.org/umbel/rc/Village" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Area108497294" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/WikicatArthurianLocations" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://umbel.org/umbel/rc/PopulatedPlace" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q486972" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://umbel.org/umbel/rc/Location_Underspecified" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/WikicatCapitalsInEurope" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#SpatialThing" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/ontology/Settlement" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/WikicatPortsAndHarbours" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/GeographicalArea108574314" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/GeographicPoint108578706" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/PhysicalEntity100001930" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/AdministrativeDistrict108491826" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/UrbanArea108675967" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/WikicatCitiesInEngland" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/WikicatPopulatedPlacesEstablishedInThe1stCentury" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Object100002684" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/WikicatCitiesWithMillionsOfInhabitants" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/District108552138" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/WikicatPostTownsInPostcodeAreasCoveringLondon" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/WikicatBritishCapitals" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Region108630985" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://schema.org/Place" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/WikicatPortCitiesAndTownsInEngland" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Site108651247" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/WikicatPortCities" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Seat108647945" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/YagoLegalActorGeo" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Tract108673395" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/YagoGeoEntity" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/YagoPermanentlyLocatedEntity" />
    <rdf:type rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/class/yago/Port108633957" />
    <rdfs:label xml:lang="es">Londres</rdfs:label>
    <rdfs:label xml:lang="nl">Londen</rdfs:label>
    <rdfs:label xml:lang="de">London</rdfs:label>
    <rdfs:label xml:lang="ja">ロンドン</rdfs:label>
    <rdfs:label xml:lang="pt">Londres</rdfs:label>
    <rdfs:label xml:lang="pl">Londyn</rdfs:label>
    <rdfs:label xml:lang="ru">Лондон</rdfs:label>
    <rdfs:label xml:lang="it">Londra</rdfs:label>
    <rdfs:label xml:lang="en">London</rdfs:label>
    <rdfs:label xml:lang="fr">Londres</rdfs:label>
    <rdfs:label xml:lang="ar">لندن</rdfs:label>
    <rdfs:label xml:lang="zh">伦敦</rdfs:label>
    <rdfs:comment xml:lang="pt">Londres (em inglês: London, AFI: [ˈlʌndən]) é a capital da Inglaterra e do Reino Unido. Por dois milênios, foi um grande povoado e sua história remonta à sua fundação pelos romanos, quando foi nomeada Londínio. O centro de Londres, a antiga City of London, também conhecida como The Square Mile (&quot;a milha quadrada&quot;) ou The City, mantém suas fronteiras medievais. Pelo menos desde o século XIX, o nome &quot;Londres&quot; se refere à metrópole desenvolvida em torno desse núcleo. Hoje, a maior parte dessa conurbação constitui a região da Grande Londres, cuja área administrativa tem seu próprio prefeito eleito e assembleia.</rdfs:comment>
    <rdfs:comment xml:lang="nl">Londen (Engels: London) is de hoofdstad en grootste stad van zowel Engeland als het Verenigd Koninkrijk. In de regio Groot-Londen, waarvan de begrenzing tegenwoordig vaak gelijk wordt gesteld aan die van de stad Londen, wonen ongeveer 7,5 miljoen mensen. Hiermee is Londen de stad met de meeste inwoners van de Europese Unie. De hele regio van de metropool strekt zich evenwel nog ver uit buiten de grenzen van Groot-Londen. De grenzen hiervan zijn niet gemakkelijk aan te geven, het aantal inwoners ligt tussen de 12 en 14 miljoen. Tussen 1831 en 1925 was Londen de grootste stad ter wereld.</rdfs:comment>
    <rdfs:comment xml:lang="it">Londra (AFI: [ˈlondra]; in inglese: London, /ˈlʌndn̩/) è la capitale e maggiore città dell&#39;Inghilterra e del Regno Unito, con i suoi 8 615 246 abitanti. Dal punto di vista del sistema urbanistico britannico viene considerata una speciale area amministrativa inglese ed è situata nella parte meridionale della Gran Bretagna. Secondo la rivista statunitense Forbes, Londra è la città più influente del mondo. Londra è la prima piazza borsistica d&#39;Europa.</rdfs:comment>
    <rdfs:comment xml:lang="de">London (deutsche Aussprache [ˈlɔndɔn], englische Aussprache [ˈlʌndən]) ist die Hauptstadt des Vereinigten Königreichs und des Landesteils England. Die Stadt liegt an der Themse in Südostengland auf der Insel Großbritannien. Das heutige Verwaltungsgebiet mit den insgesamt 33 Stadtbezirken entstand 1965 mit der Gründung von Greater London. Dort lebten 2014 laut Schätzung rund 8,5 Millionen Menschen, davon rund 3,3 Millionen in den 13 Stadtbezirken von Inner London. London ist damit die bevölkerungsreichste Stadt der Europäischen Union sowie mit 13,6 Millionen Menschen in der London Metropolitan Area noch vor Paris (12,3 Millionen Einwohner) die größte Metropolregion der EU.</rdfs:comment>
    <rdfs:comment xml:lang="pl">Londyn (ang. London) – miasto będące stolicą Wielkiej Brytanii i Anglii położone w jej południowo-wschodniej części. Położony nad Tamizą, jest trzecim największym miastem Europy po Moskwie i Stambule; jest także największym miastem Unii Europejskiej i jednym z większych miast świata zarówno w skali samego miasta, jak i aglomeracji. Liczba mieszkańców Londynu (w granicach tzw. Wielkiego Londynu) wynosi ok. 8,4 mln (2013 r.) na obszarze 1572 km²; cała zaś aglomeracja londyńska, łącznie ze wszystkimi przyległymi miejscowościami liczy ok. 13 mln mieszkańców (obszar tzw. metropolia). Około 20% mieszkańców pochodzi z Azji, Afryki i Karaibów.</rdfs:comment>
    <rdfs:comment xml:lang="ru">Ло́ндон (англ. London [ˈlʌndən] (инф.)) — столица и крупнейший город Соединённого Королевства Великобритании и Северной Ирландии. Административно образует регион Англии Большой Лондон, разделённый на 33 самоуправляемых района. Население составляет 8,6 млн человек (2015 год), второй по величине город Европы и крупнейший в Евросоюзе. Образует агломерацию «Большой Лондон» и более обширный метрополитенский район. Расположен на юго-востоке острова Великобритания, на равнине Лондонского бассейна, в устье Темзы вблизи Северного моря.</rdfs:comment>
    <rdfs:comment xml:lang="ar">لندن (وقيل كذلك لُوندَرَس ولندرة ولندرا) هي عاصمة المملكة المتحدة وأكبر مدنها. تقع على نهر التيمز في جنوب بريطانيا. يعيش في المدينة حوالي 8.4 مليون نسمة، منهم حوالي 2.7 في أحياء لندن الداخلية. يبلغ عدد سكانها مع ضواحيها 15,010,295 نسمة في 2012، لتكون بذلك أكبر مدن أوروبا، وأحد أهم مراكزها السياسية والاقتصادية والثقافية. شكل التقسيم الإداري الحالي للندن في 1 أبريل 1965 مع تأسيس لندن الكبرى. يوجد في المدينة عدد كبير من الجامعات والمعاهد والمتاحف والمسارح. كما تتخذ كثير من المنظمات الدولية والشركات العالمية من المدينة مقراً لها، وبالتحديد المدينة الأصلية « مدينة لندن » ذات الإدارة المستقلة عن أغلب مناطق العاصمة.</rdfs:comment>
    <rdfs:comment xml:lang="fr">Londres (prononcé [lɔ̃dʁ] ; en anglais London [ˈlʌn.dən]), située dans le Sud-Est de la Grande-Bretagne, est la capitale et la plus grande ville du Royaume-Uni ; longtemps capitale de l&#39;Empire britannique, elle est désormais le siège du Commonwealth.</rdfs:comment>
    <rdfs:comment xml:lang="en">London /ˈlʌndən/ is the capital and most populous city of England and the United Kingdom. Standing on the River Thames in the south east of the island of Great Britain, London has been a major settlement for two millennia. It was founded by the Romans, who named it Londinium. London&#39;s ancient core, the City of London, largely retains its 1.12-square-mile (2.9 km2) medieval boundaries. Since at least the 19th century, &quot;London&quot; has also referred to the metropolis around this core, historically split between Middlesex, Essex, Surrey, Kent, and Hertfordshire, which today largely makes up Greater London, governed by the Mayor of London and the London Assembly.</rdfs:comment>
    <rdfs:comment xml:lang="ja">ロンドン（英語: London、英語発音: [ˈlʌndən]）は、グレートブリテンおよび北アイルランド連合王国およびこれを構成するイングランドの首都。イギリスや欧州連合域内で最大の都市圏を形成している。ロンドンはテムズ川河畔に位置し、2,000年前のローマ帝国によるロンディニウム創建が都市の起源である。ロンディニウム当時の街の中心部は、現在のシティ・オブ・ロンドン（シティ）に当たる地域にあった。シティの市街壁内の面積は約1平方マイルあり、中世以来その範囲はほぼ変わっていない。少なくとも19世紀以降、「ロンドン」の名称はシティの市街壁を越えて開発が進んだシティ周辺地域をも含めて用いられている。ロンドンは市街地の大部分はコナベーションにより形成されている。ロンドンを管轄するリージョンであるグレーター・ロンドンでは、選挙で選出されたロンドン市長とロンドン議会により統治が行われている。 首都とされているが、他国の多くの首都と同様、ロンドンの首都としての地位を明示した文書は存在しない。</rdfs:comment>
    <rdfs:comment xml:lang="es">Londres (London en inglés, Acerca de este sonido ˈlʌndən (?·i)) es la capital de Inglaterra y del Reino Unido, y la mayor ciudad y área urbana de Gran Bretaña y de toda la Unión Europea. Situada a orillas del río Támesis, Londres es un importante asentamiento humano desde que fue fundada por los romanos con el nombre de Londinium hace casi dos milenios. El núcleo antiguo de la urbe, la City de Londres, conserva básicamente su perímetro medieval de una milla cuadrada. Desde el siglo XIX el nombre «Londres» también hace referencia a toda la metrópolis desarrollada alrededor de este núcleo. El grueso de esta conurbación forma la región de Londres y el área administrativa del Gran Londres, gobernado por el alcalde y la asamblea de Londres.</rdfs:comment>
    <rdfs:seeAlso rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Greater_London" />
    <rdfs:seeAlso rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/List_of_annual_events" />
    <rdfs:seeAlso rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/List_of_Sites_of_Special_Scientific_Interest" />
    <rdfs:seeAlso rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/London" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://linkedgeodata.org/triplify/node107775" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://es.dbpedia.org/resource/Londres" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://it.dbpedia.org/resource/Londra" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://ko.dbpedia.org/resource/런던" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://pt.dbpedia.org/resource/Londres" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://cs.dbpedia.org/resource/Londýn" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://sws.geonames.org/2643743/" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://rdf.freebase.com/ns/m.04jpl" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://pl.dbpedia.org/resource/Londyn" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://eu.dbpedia.org/resource/Londres" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/London" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://de.dbpedia.org/resource/London" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://fr.dbpedia.org/resource/Londres" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://ja.dbpedia.org/resource/ロンドン" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://dati.camera.it/ocd/luogo.rdf/londra_regno-unito" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://data.nytimes.com/14085781296239331901" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://id.dbpedia.org/resource/London" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q84" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://sw.cyc.com/concept/Mx4rvVjWPJwpEbGdrcN5Y29ycA" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://d-nb.info/gnd/4074335-4" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://wikidata.dbpedia.org/resource/Q84" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://nl.dbpedia.org/resource/Londen" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://linked-web-apis.fit.cvut.cz/resource/london_city" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://linked-web-apis.fit.cvut.cz/resource/london_uk_city" />
    <owl:sameAs rdf:resource="http://el.dbpedia.org/resource/Λονδίνο" />
    <dct:subject rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Category:University_towns_in_the_United_Kingdom" />
    <dct:subject rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Category:British_capitals" />
    <dct:subject rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Category:Staple_ports" />
    <dct:subject rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Category:London" />
    <dct:subject rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Category:Capitals_in_Europe" />
    <dct:subject rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Category:Articles_including_recorded_pronunciations_(UK_English)" />
    <dct:subject rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Category:Port_cities_and_towns_in_England" />
    <dct:subject rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Category:Populated_places_established_in_the_1st_century" />
    <dbo:wikiPageID rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">17867</dbo:wikiPageID>
    <dbo:wikiPageRevisionID rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">745294300</dbo:wikiPageRevisionID>
    <dbo:wikiPageExternalLink rdf:resource="http://mapoflondon.uvic.ca/" />
    <dbo:wikiPageExternalLink rdf:resource="http://www.london.gov.uk/" />
    <dbo:wikiPageExternalLink rdf:resource="http://www.britishpathe.com/search/query/london" />
    <dbo:wikiPageExternalLink rdf:resource="http://www.tfl.gov.uk/" />
    <dbo:wikiPageExternalLink rdf:resource="http://www.british-history.ac.uk/place.aspx?region=1" />
    <dbo:wikiPageExternalLink rdf:resource="http://www.museumoflondon.org.uk/" />
    <dbo:wikiPageExternalLink rdf:resource="http://www.visitlondon.com/" />
    <dbo:wikiPageExternalLink rdf:resource="https://london.gov.uk/" />
    <foaf:name xml:lang="en">London</foaf:name>
    <foaf:homepage rdf:resource="https://london.gov.uk/" />
    <geo:lat rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#float">51.5072</geo:lat>
    <geo:long rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#float">-0.1275</geo:long>
    <foaf:depiction rdf:resource="http://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/Special:FilePath/London_Montage_L.jpg" />
    <foaf:isPrimaryTopicOf rdf:resource="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/London" />
    <geo:geometry rdf:datatype="http://www.openlinksw.com/schemas/virtrdf#Geometry">POINT(-0.12749999761581 51.507221221924)</geo:geometry>
    <dbo:thumbnail rdf:resource="http://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/Special:FilePath/London_Montage_L.jpg?width=300" />
    <prov:wasDerivedFrom rdf:resource="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/London?oldid=745294300" />
    <ns8:areaTotal rdf:datatype="http://dbpedia.org/datatype/squareKilometre">1572.0</ns8:areaTotal>
    <ns8:populationDensity rdf:datatype="http://dbpedia.org/datatype/inhabitantsPerSquareKilometre">5518.0</ns8:populationDensity>
    <dbo:abstract xml:lang="ar">لندن (وقيل كذلك لُوندَرَس ولندرة ولندرا) هي عاصمة المملكة المتحدة وأكبر مدنها. تقع على نهر التيمز في جنوب بريطانيا. يعيش في المدينة حوالي 8.4 مليون نسمة، منهم حوالي 2.7 في أحياء لندن الداخلية. يبلغ عدد سكانها مع ضواحيها 15,010,295 نسمة في 2012، لتكون بذلك أكبر مدن أوروبا، وأحد أهم مراكزها السياسية والاقتصادية والثقافية. شكل التقسيم الإداري الحالي للندن في 1 أبريل 1965 مع تأسيس لندن الكبرى. يوجد في المدينة عدد كبير من الجامعات والمعاهد والمتاحف والمسارح. كما تتخذ كثير من المنظمات الدولية والشركات العالمية من المدينة مقراً لها، وبالتحديد المدينة الأصلية « مدينة لندن » ذات الإدارة المستقلة عن أغلب مناطق العاصمة.</dbo:abstract>
    <dbo:abstract xml:lang="ru">Ло́ндон (англ. London [ˈlʌndən] (инф.)) — столица и крупнейший город Соединённого Королевства Великобритании и Северной Ирландии. Административно образует регион Англии Большой Лондон, разделённый на 33 самоуправляемых района. Население составляет 8,6 млн человек (2015 год), второй по величине город Европы и крупнейший в Евросоюзе. Образует агломерацию «Большой Лондон» и более обширный метрополитенский район. Расположен на юго-востоке острова Великобритания, на равнине Лондонского бассейна, в устье Темзы вблизи Северного моря. Главный политический, экономический и культурный центр Великобритании. Экономика города занимает пятую часть экономики страны. Относится к глобальным городам высшего ранга, ведущим мировым финансовым центрам. Исторический центр, образованный районами Вестминстер и Сити, сложился в Викторианскую эпоху. Среди единичных построек, уцелевших после пожара 1666 года, — средневековая крепость Тауэр. Основан около 43 года под названием Лондиниум римлянами вскоре после их вторжения в Британию. В I—III веках — столица римской Британии, с XI—XII веков — Англии, с 1707 года — Великобритании, с XVI по XX век — Британской империи. С 1825 по 1925 год был крупнейшим городом мира.</dbo:abstract>
    <dbo:abstract xml:lang="en">London /ˈlʌndən/ is the capital and most populous city of England and the United Kingdom. Standing on the River Thames in the south east of the island of Great Britain, London has been a major settlement for two millennia. It was founded by the Romans, who named it Londinium. London&#39;s ancient core, the City of London, largely retains its 1.12-square-mile (2.9 km2) medieval boundaries. Since at least the 19th century, &quot;London&quot; has also referred to the metropolis around this core, historically split between Middlesex, Essex, Surrey, Kent, and Hertfordshire, which today largely makes up Greater London, governed by the Mayor of London and the London Assembly. As a Nylonkong metropolis, London is a leading global city, in the arts, commerce, education, entertainment, fashion, finance, healthcare, media, professional services, research and development, tourism, and transport. It is one of the world&#39;s leading financial centres and has the fifth- or sixth-largest metropolitan area GDP in the world. London is a world cultural capital. It is the world&#39;s most-visited city as measured by international arrivals and has the world&#39;s largest city airport system measured by passenger traffic. London is the world&#39;s leading investment destination, hosting more international retailers and ultra high-net-worth individuals than any other city. London&#39;s universities form the largest concentration of higher education institutes in Europe, and a 2014 report placed it first in the world university rankings. According to the report London also ranks first in the world in software, multimedia development and design, and shares first position in technology readiness. In 2012, London became the only city to host the modern Summer Olympic Games three times. London has a diverse range of people and cultures, and more than 300 languages are spoken in the region. Its estimated mid-2015 municipal population (corresponding to Greater London) was 8,673,713, the largest of any city in the European Union, and accounting for 12.5 per cent of the UK population. London&#39;s urban area is the second most populous in the EU, after Paris, with 9,787,426 inhabitants at the 2011 census. The city&#39;s metropolitan area is one of the most populous in Europe with 13,879,757 inhabitants, while the Greater London Authority states the population of the city-region (covering a large part of the south east) as 22.7 million.London was the world&#39;s most populous city from around 1831 to 1925. London contains four World Heritage Sites: the Tower of London; Kew Gardens; the site comprising the Palace of Westminster, Westminster Abbey, and St Margaret&#39;s Church; and the historic settlement of Greenwich (in which the Royal Observatory, Greenwich marks the Prime Meridian, 0° longitude, and GMT). Other famous landmarks include Buckingham Palace, the London Eye, Piccadilly Circus, St Paul&#39;s Cathedral, Tower Bridge, Trafalgar Square, and The Shard. London is home to numerous museums, galleries, libraries, sporting events and other cultural institutions, including the British Museum, National Gallery, Natural History Museum, Tate Modern, British Library and West End theatres. The London Underground is the oldest underground railway network in the world.</dbo:abstract>
    <dbo:abstract xml:lang="nl">Londen (Engels: London) is de hoofdstad en grootste stad van zowel Engeland als het Verenigd Koninkrijk. In de regio Groot-Londen, waarvan de begrenzing tegenwoordig vaak gelijk wordt gesteld aan die van de stad Londen, wonen ongeveer 7,5 miljoen mensen. Hiermee is Londen de stad met de meeste inwoners van de Europese Unie. De hele regio van de metropool strekt zich evenwel nog ver uit buiten de grenzen van Groot-Londen. De grenzen hiervan zijn niet gemakkelijk aan te geven, het aantal inwoners ligt tussen de 12 en 14 miljoen. Tussen 1831 en 1925 was Londen de grootste stad ter wereld. De stad is, behalve de hoofdstad en de grootste stad van het Verenigd Koninkrijk, ook het politieke, economische en culturele centrum van dat land. Ook in Europa en de wereld vervult ze een belangrijke functie op diverse gebieden: Londen wordt als een van de vier traditionele alfa-wereldsteden beschouwd, samen met Parijs, Tokio en New York. Vooral in de 18e en de 19e eeuw was Londen als hoofdstad van het Britse Rijk het absolute politieke en economische machtscentrum van de wereld. Londen telt vier plaatsen die op de Werelderfgoedlijst van de UNESCO staan: de Tower of London, de historische nederzetting van Greenwich, de Kew Gardens, en een gezamenlijke inschrijving bestaande uit het Palace of Westminster, Westminster Abbey en Saint Margaret&#39;s Church.</dbo:abstract>
    <dbo:abstract xml:lang="es">Londres (London en inglés, Acerca de este sonido ˈlʌndən (?·i)) es la capital de Inglaterra y del Reino Unido, y la mayor ciudad y área urbana de Gran Bretaña y de toda la Unión Europea. Situada a orillas del río Támesis, Londres es un importante asentamiento humano desde que fue fundada por los romanos con el nombre de Londinium hace casi dos milenios. El núcleo antiguo de la urbe, la City de Londres, conserva básicamente su perímetro medieval de una milla cuadrada. Desde el siglo XIX el nombre «Londres» también hace referencia a toda la metrópolis desarrollada alrededor de este núcleo. El grueso de esta conurbación forma la región de Londres y el área administrativa del Gran Londres, gobernado por el alcalde y la asamblea de Londres. Londres es una ciudad global, uno de los centros neurálgicos en el ámbito de las artes, el comercio, la educación, el entretenimiento, la moda, las finanzas, los medios de comunicación, la investigación, el turismo o el transporte. Es el principal centro financiero del mundo y una de las áreas metropolitanas con mayor PIB. Londres es también una capital cultural mundial, la ciudad más visitada considerando el número de visitas internacionales y tiene el mayor sistema aeroportuario del mundo según el tráfico de pasajeros. Asimismo, las 43 universidades de la ciudad conforman la mayor concentración de centros de estudios superiores de toda Europa. En el año 2012 Londres se convirtió en la única ciudad en albergar la celebración de tres Juegos Olímpicos de Verano. En esta ciudad multirracial convive gente de un gran número de culturas que hablan más de trescientos idiomas distintos. La Autoridad del Gran Londres estima que en 2015 la ciudad tiene 8,63 millones de habitantes, una cifra que la convierte en el municipio más populoso de la Unión Europea y que supone el 12,5 % del total de habitantes del Reino Unido. El área urbana del Gran Londres, con 8 278 251 habitantes, es la segunda más grande de Europa, pero su área metropolitana, con una población estimada de entre 12 y 14 millones, es la mayor del continente. Desde 1831 a 1925 Londres, como capital del Imperio británico, fue la ciudad más populosa del mundo. Londres cuenta con cuatro enclaves declarados Patrimonio de la Humanidad: la Torre de Londres, el Real Jardín Botánico de Kew, el sitio formado por el Palacio, la Abadía de Westminster, la Iglesia de Santa Margarita y Greenwich (donde se encuentra el Real Observatorio que marca el meridiano de Greenwich y el tiempo medio). Otros lugares famosos de la ciudad son el Palacio de Buckingham, el London Eye, Piccadilly Circus, la Catedral de San Pablo, el Puente de la Torre o Trafalgar Square. Londres cuenta también con numerosos museos, galerías de arte, bibliotecas, eventos deportivos y otras instituciones culturales como el Museo Británico, la National Gallery, la Tate Modern, la Biblioteca Británica y los cuarenta teatros del West End. El metro de Londres, que en 2013 cumplió 150 años, es el más antiguo del mundo.</dbo:abstract>
    <dbo:abstract xml:lang="pt">Londres (em inglês: London, AFI: [ˈlʌndən]) é a capital da Inglaterra e do Reino Unido. Por dois milênios, foi um grande povoado e sua história remonta à sua fundação pelos romanos, quando foi nomeada Londínio. O centro de Londres, a antiga City of London, também conhecida como The Square Mile (&quot;a milha quadrada&quot;) ou The City, mantém suas fronteiras medievais. Pelo menos desde o século XIX, o nome &quot;Londres&quot; se refere à metrópole desenvolvida em torno desse núcleo. Hoje, a maior parte dessa conurbação constitui a região da Grande Londres, cuja área administrativa tem seu próprio prefeito eleito e assembleia. Londres é uma importante cidade global (ao lado de Nova Iorque, Tóquio e Paris) e é um dos maiores, mais importantes e influentes centros financeiros do mundo. O centro de Londres abriga a sede de mais da metade das 100 melhores companhias do Reino Unido (o índice FTSE 100) e mais de 100 das 500 maiores da Europa. Londres possui forte influência na política, finanças, educação, entretenimento, mídia, moda, artes e cultura em geral, o que contribui para a sua posição global. É um importante destino turístico para visitantes nacionais e estrangeiros. Londres sediou os Jogos Olímpicos de Verão de 1908, 1948 e 2012. Londres tem uma gama diversa de povos, culturas e religiões e mais de 300 idiomas são falados em seu território. Em julho de 2007, a população oficial era de 7 556 900 habitantes dentro dos limites de Londres, tornando-se o município mais populoso da União Europeia. Sua área urbana (a segunda maior da UE) tem uma população de 8 278 251 habitantes, enquanto a região metropolitana (a maior da UE) tem uma população total (rural e urbana) estimada entre 12 milhões e 14 milhões de habitantes. O Metrô de Londres, administrado pela Transport for London, é a mais extensa rede ferroviária subterrânea do mundo, o Aeroporto de Londres Heathrow é o aeroporto mais movimentado do mundo em número de passageiros internacionais. e o espaço aéreo da cidade é o mais movimentado do qualquer outro centro urbano do mundo. A cidade possui quatro Patrimônios Mundiais: a Torre de Londres; os Reais Jardins Botânicos de Kew; o local que compreende o Palácio de Westminster, a Abadia de Westminster e a Igreja de Santa Margarida; e o local histórico de Greenwich (onde o Observatório Real de Greenwich marca o meridiano primário, 0° longitude e GMT). Outros marcos famosos incluem o Palácio de Buckingham, a London Eye, Piccadilly Circus, a Catedral de São Paulo, a Tower Bridge, a Trafalgar Square e o The Shard. Londres é a sede de inúmeros museus, galerias, bibliotecas e outras instituições culturais, como o Museu Britânico, a National Gallery, Tate Modern e a Biblioteca Britânica. O metrô de Londres é a mais antiga rede ferroviária subterrânea do mundo.</dbo:abstract>
    <dbo:abstract xml:lang="it">Londra (AFI: [ˈlondra]; in inglese: London, /ˈlʌndn̩/) è la capitale e maggiore città dell&#39;Inghilterra e del Regno Unito, con i suoi 8 615 246 abitanti. Dal punto di vista del sistema urbanistico britannico viene considerata una speciale area amministrativa inglese ed è situata nella parte meridionale della Gran Bretagna. La sua estensione superficiale la rende la città più estesa d&#39;Europa, seguita da Roma e Berlino, ed è la città più popolata dell&#39;Unione europea (in Europa superata solo da Istanbul e Mosca): l&#39;area metropolitana conta infatti circa 14 milioni di residenti e si estende per svariate decine di chilometri lungo la valle del Tamigi, fino al suo enorme estuario. Metropoli multietnica, molti degli abitanti, chiamati londinesi (londoners), provengono dall&#39;estero o sono di origine straniera, risultando così una delle città più cosmopolite del mondo. Londra è stata la capitale indiscussa dell&#39;Impero Britannico, e quindi meta di flussi migratori durante e soprattutto dopo l&#39;era coloniale. Secondo la rivista statunitense Forbes, Londra è la città più influente del mondo. Londra è la prima piazza borsistica d&#39;Europa. Ha il più elevato PIL fra tutte le città europee, ed il quinto al mondo. I suoi cinque aeroporti internazionali ne fanno il più grande snodo del traffico aereo globale; è anche sede del più antico sistema di metropolitana del mondo, la London Underground (The Tube). È la quarta città più visitata al mondo dal turismo internazionale. A Londra hanno sede numerose istituzioni, organizzazioni e società internazionali. Vi si trovano importanti musei, teatri e sale da concerto; la città contiene quattro patrimoni dell&#39;umanità. Inoltre, vi risiede stabilmente il monarca del Regno Unito presso Buckingham Palace ed il parlamento; il primo ministro occupa l&#39;abitazione a 10 Downing Street. Per tutte le caratteristiche elencate, Londra conquista il titolo di Città globale, classificandosi come l&#39;unica città britannica nella lista delle Città Mondiali Alfa. Dal 2000, con le riforme volute dal governo di Tony Blair, Londra è amministrata in maniera federale da un&#39;unica autorità centrale, la Greater London Authority con un proprio sindaco e una propria Assemblea, e da 33 quartieri londinesi, tra cui la Città di Londra e la Città di Westminster. Attualmente il concetto di Londra capitale è da riferirsi alla Grande Londra e non alla sola city, tant&#39;è che tutte le istituzioni governative (a partire dall&#39;incoronazione del re nell&#39;Abbazia di Westminster) hanno sede nella città di Westminster.</dbo:abstract>
    <dbo:abstract xml:lang="pl">Londyn (ang. London) – miasto będące stolicą Wielkiej Brytanii i Anglii położone w jej południowo-wschodniej części. Położony nad Tamizą, jest trzecim największym miastem Europy po Moskwie i Stambule; jest także największym miastem Unii Europejskiej i jednym z większych miast świata zarówno w skali samego miasta, jak i aglomeracji. Liczba mieszkańców Londynu (w granicach tzw. Wielkiego Londynu) wynosi ok. 8,4 mln (2013 r.) na obszarze 1572 km²; cała zaś aglomeracja londyńska, łącznie ze wszystkimi przyległymi miejscowościami liczy ok. 13 mln mieszkańców (obszar tzw. metropolia). Około 20% mieszkańców pochodzi z Azji, Afryki i Karaibów. Współczesny Londyn jest największym centrum finansowym świata (od 2006 przed Nowym Jorkiem). Tutaj dokonuje się 30% światowego obrotu walutami i 40% światowego obrotu euroobligacjami. W Londynie usytuowanych jest kilkaset banków, największa giełda w Europie (trzecia na świecie), liczne towarzystwa ubezpieczeniowe i inwestycyjne. Londyn jest także ogromnym ośrodkiem medialnym. Jest to także jedno z najbardziej zanieczyszczonych miast Unii Europejskiej. Miasto przyciąga rocznie ok. 30 mln turystów.</dbo:abstract>
    <dbo:abstract xml:lang="ja">ロンドン（英語: London、英語発音: [ˈlʌndən]）は、グレートブリテンおよび北アイルランド連合王国およびこれを構成するイングランドの首都。イギリスや欧州連合域内で最大の都市圏を形成している。ロンドンはテムズ川河畔に位置し、2,000年前のローマ帝国によるロンディニウム創建が都市の起源である。ロンディニウム当時の街の中心部は、現在のシティ・オブ・ロンドン（シティ）に当たる地域にあった。シティの市街壁内の面積は約1平方マイルあり、中世以来その範囲はほぼ変わっていない。少なくとも19世紀以降、「ロンドン」の名称はシティの市街壁を越えて開発が進んだシティ周辺地域をも含めて用いられている。ロンドンは市街地の大部分はコナベーションにより形成されている。ロンドンを管轄するリージョンであるグレーター・ロンドンでは、選挙で選出されたロンドン市長とロンドン議会により統治が行われている。 ロンドンは屈指の世界都市として、芸術、商業、教育、娯楽、ファッション、金融、ヘルスケア、メディア、専門サービス、調査開発、観光、交通といった広範囲にわたる分野において強い影響力がある。また、ニューヨークと並び世界をリードする金融センターでもあり、2009年時点の域内総生産は世界第5位で、欧州域内では最大である。世界的な文化の中心でもある。ロンドンは世界で最も来訪者の多い都市であり、単一の都市圏としては世界で最も航空旅客数が多い。欧州では最も高等教育機関が集積する都市であり、ロンドンには大学が43校ある。2012年のロンドンオリンピック開催に伴い、1908年、1948年に次ぐ3度目のオリンピック開催となり、同一都市としては史上最多となる。 ロンドンは文化的な多様性があり、300以上の言語が使われている。2011年3月時点のロンドンの公式の人口は8,174,100人であり、欧州連合の市域人口では最大で、イギリス国内の全人口の12.7%を占めている。グレーター・ロンドンの都市的地域は、パリの都市的地域に次いで欧州連合域内で第2位となる8,278,251人の人口を有し、ロンドンの都市圏の人口は1,200万人から1,400万人に達し、欧州域内では最大である。ロンドンは1831年から1925年にかけて、世界最大の人口を擁する都市であった。2012年にマスターカードが公表した統計によると、ロンドンは世界で最も外国人旅行者が訪れる都市である。 首都とされているが、他国の多くの首都と同様、ロンドンの首都としての地位を明示した文書は存在しない。</dbo:abstract>
    <dbo:abstract xml:lang="fr">Londres (prononcé [lɔ̃dʁ] ; en anglais London [ˈlʌn.dən]), située dans le Sud-Est de la Grande-Bretagne, est la capitale et la plus grande ville du Royaume-Uni ; longtemps capitale de l&#39;Empire britannique, elle est désormais le siège du Commonwealth. Fondée il y a presque 2 000 ans par les Romains sous le nom de Londinium, Londres était au XIXe siècle la ville la plus peuplée du monde. Bien que largement dépassée dans ce domaine par de nombreuses mégapoles, elle reste une métropole de tout premier plan, en raison de son rayonnement et de sa puissance économique, dû notamment à sa place de premier centre financier mondial. Londres se place dans le rang des grands centres financiers et culturels du monde avec New York et Hong Kong, cette trilogie est appelée par les médias anglophones « Nylonkong ». La région de Londres, composée de l&#39;Inner London et de l&#39;Outer London, comptait environ 8 615 000 habitants en 2014 et réalise un cinquième du produit intérieur brut du Royaume-Uni. En 2012, l&#39;aire urbaine de Londres comptait 8 416 535 habitants, son agglomération 11 140 445 et son aire métropolitaine (zone urbaine élargie ou zone d&#39;influence directe) 12 317 800 d&#39;habitants. En Europe, seules les agglomérations de Moscou, Istanbul et Paris ont un poids démographique comparable. Ses habitants s&#39;appellent les Londoniens (en anglais : Londoners). Londres, seule ville à avoir organisé trois fois les Jeux olympiques (1908, 1948, 2012), est dynamique et très diverse sur le plan culturel. Elle joue un rôle important dans l&#39;art et dans la mode. Elle reçoit 28 millions de touristes par an et compte quatre sites inscrits au patrimoine mondial ainsi que de nombreux monuments emblématiques : le Palais de Westminster, le Tower Bridge, la Tour de Londres, l&#39;Abbaye de Westminster, le Palais de Buckingham, ainsi que des institutions renommées comme le British Museum ou la National Gallery.</dbo:abstract>
    <dbo:abstract xml:lang="de">London (deutsche Aussprache [ˈlɔndɔn], englische Aussprache [ˈlʌndən]) ist die Hauptstadt des Vereinigten Königreichs und des Landesteils England. Die Stadt liegt an der Themse in Südostengland auf der Insel Großbritannien. Das heutige Verwaltungsgebiet mit den insgesamt 33 Stadtbezirken entstand 1965 mit der Gründung von Greater London. Dort lebten 2014 laut Schätzung rund 8,5 Millionen Menschen, davon rund 3,3 Millionen in den 13 Stadtbezirken von Inner London. London ist damit die bevölkerungsreichste Stadt der Europäischen Union sowie mit 13,6 Millionen Menschen in der London Metropolitan Area noch vor Paris (12,3 Millionen Einwohner) die größte Metropolregion der EU. Im Jahre 50 n. Chr. von den Römern als antike Siedlung „Londinium“ gegründet, wurde die Stadt nach der normannischen Eroberung 1066 zur Hauptstadt des Königreichs England und in Folge Sitz des britischen Königshauses. Bereits im Mittelalter wurde London zu einem bedeutenden Handelsplatz in Europa. Unter der Herrschaft von Elisabeth I. im 16. Jahrhundert stieg ihre Bedeutung als Hafenstadt der Nordsee. Durch den Beginn der Industrialisierung im 18. Jahrhundert wuchs auch die Bevölkerung Londons, sodass die Stadt um 1800 als eine der ersten die Grenze von einer Million Einwohnern überstieg. Bis 1900 versechsfachte sich die Bevölkerung und London wurde im 19. Jahrhundert nicht nur zur Hauptstadt des Britischen Weltreiches, sondern überdies zur größten Stadt der Welt, die sie bis 1925 blieb. Sie entwickelte sich zu einer bedeutenden Stadt der Technik und Industrie sowie der Politik, womit sie bis heute zu den Weltstädten zählt. London ist gegenwärtig eines der bedeutendsten Kultur- und Handelszentren der Welt mit zahlreichen Universitäten, Hochschulen, Theatern und Museen. Mit der City of London zählt die Stadt außerdem neben New York City und Frankfurt am Main zu den größten Finanzplätzen der Welt. Historische Gebäude wie der Palace of Westminster oder Tower of London zählen unter anderen zum UNESCO-Weltkulturerbe. Mit jährlich bis zu 18 Millionen Touristen aus dem Ausland ist London seit 2014 vor Paris und Bangkok die meistbesuchte Stadt weltweit.</dbo:abstract>
    <dbo:areaTotal rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">1.572e+09</dbo:areaTotal>
    <dbo:country rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/United_Kingdom" />
    <dbo:elevation rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">35.0</dbo:elevation>
    <dbo:governingBody rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Greater_London_Authority" />
    <dbo:governmentType rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Devolution_in_the_United_Kingdom" />
    <dbo:isPartOf rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Greater_London" />
    <dbo:isPartOf rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/England" />
    <dbo:leaderName rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/London_Assembly" />
    <dbo:leaderName rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/London_Assembly_constituencies" />
    <dbo:leaderName rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Sadiq_Khan" />
    <dbo:leaderName rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/London_(European_Parliament_constituency)" />
    <dbo:leaderName rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/List_of_Parliamentary_constituencies_in_London" />
    <dbo:leaderTitle xml:lang="en">Elected body</dbo:leaderTitle>
    <dbo:leaderTitle xml:lang="en">UK Parliament</dbo:leaderTitle>
    <dbo:leaderTitle xml:lang="en">Mayor</dbo:leaderTitle>
    <dbo:leaderTitle xml:lang="en">European Parliament</dbo:leaderTitle>
    <dbo:leaderTitle xml:lang="en">London Assembly</dbo:leaderTitle>
    <dbo:populationDensity rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">5518.0</dbo:populationDensity>
    <dbo:populationTotal rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#nonNegativeInteger">8673713</dbo:populationTotal>
    <dbo:timeZone rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Greenwich_Mean_Time" />
    <dbo:timeZone rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/British_Summer_Time" />
    <dbo:utcOffset>±00:00UTC</dbo:utcOffset>
    <dbo:utcOffset>+1</dbo:utcOffset>
    <georss:point>51.507222222222225 -0.1275</georss:point>
    <dbp:align rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">right</dbp:align>
    <dbp:align rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">left</dbp:align>
    <dbp:alt rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Asian</dbp:alt>
    <dbp:alt rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Lake with London Eye in the background</dbp:alt>
    <dbp:alt rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Hyde Park</dbp:alt>
    <dbp:alt rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Black</dbp:alt>
    <dbp:alt rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">White</dbp:alt>
    <dbp:alt rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">London montage. Clicking on an image in the picture causes the browser to load the appropriate article.
rect 217 123 282 330 Heron Tower
rect 322 123 380 330 Tower 42
rect 441 154 498 330 30 St Mary Axe
rect 505 87 572 330 Leadenhall Building
rect 638 208 699 251 Willis Building
rect 596 251 715 332 Lloyds Building
rect 740 217 851 275 Canary Wharf
rect 888 168 940 330 20 Fenchurch Street
rect 0 330 1200 450 City of London
rect 0 460 330 1420 London Underground
rect 330 460 622 1420 Elizabeth Tower
rect 632 460 1200 951 Trafalgar Square
rect 632 961 1200 1420 London Eye
rect 0 1429 1200 1765 Tower Bridge
rect 0 1765 1200 1809 River Thames</dbp:alt>
    <dbp:aprHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">14.2</dbp:aprHighC>
    <dbp:aprHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">15.7</dbp:aprHighC>
    <dbp:aprLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">5.5</dbp:aprLowC>
    <dbp:aprLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.2</dbp:aprLowC>
    <dbp:aprMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">12</dbp:aprMeanC>
    <dbp:aprPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">9.1</dbp:aprPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:aprPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">43.7</dbp:aprPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:aprRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">29.4</dbp:aprRecordHighC>
    <dbp:aprRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">-2.6</dbp:aprRecordLowC>
    <dbp:aprSun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">168.7</dbp:aprSun>
    <dbp:areaBlank1Km rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">1737.9</dbp:areaBlank1Km>
    <dbp:areaBlank1Title rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Greater_London_Urban_Area" />
    <dbp:areaBlank2Km rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8382</dbp:areaBlank2Km>
    <dbp:areaBlank2Title rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/London_metropolitan_area" />
    <dbp:augHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">23.2</dbp:augHighC>
    <dbp:augLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">15.5</dbp:augLowC>
    <dbp:augLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">13.7</dbp:augLowC>
    <dbp:augMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">19.4</dbp:augMeanC>
    <dbp:augPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">7.5</dbp:augPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:augPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">49.5</dbp:augPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:augRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">38.1</dbp:augRecordHighC>
    <dbp:augRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">5.9</dbp:augRecordLowC>
    <dbp:augSun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">204.7</dbp:augSun>
    <dbp:blank1Info rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/London_City_Airport" />
    <dbp:blank1Info rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/London_Southend_Airport" />
    <dbp:blank1Info rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/London_Stansted_Airport" />
    <dbp:blank1Info rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Gatwick_Airport" />
    <dbp:blank1Info rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Luton_Airport" />
    <dbp:blank1Info rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/London_Heathrow_Airport" />
    <dbp:blank1Name rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">International airports</dbp:blank1Name>
    <dbp:blankInfo rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">City of London Police and Metropolitan Police</dbp:blankInfo>
    <dbp:blankInfoSec rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/.london" />
    <dbp:blankName rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Police</dbp:blankName>
    <dbp:blankNameSec rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/GeoTLD" />
    <dbp:caption rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Black</dbp:caption>
    <dbp:caption rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">St. James&#39;s Park lake with the London Eye in the distance</dbp:caption>
    <dbp:caption rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Ethnic groups in the 2011 census</dbp:caption>
    <dbp:caption rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">White</dbp:caption>
    <dbp:caption rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Aerial view of Hyde Park</dbp:caption>
    <dbp:caption rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Asian</dbp:caption>
    <dbp:captionAlign rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">center</dbp:captionAlign>
    <dbp:color rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Blue</dbp:color>
    <dbp:color rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Green</dbp:color>
    <dbp:color rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Red</dbp:color>
    <dbp:color rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Yellow</dbp:color>
    <dbp:color rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Orange</dbp:color>
    <dbp:color rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Purple</dbp:color>
    <dbp:coordinatesDisplay rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">inline,title</dbp:coordinatesDisplay>
    <dbp:coordinatesRegion rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">GB</dbp:coordinatesRegion>
    <dbp:decHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.3</dbp:decHighC>
    <dbp:decHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.6</dbp:decHighC>
    <dbp:decLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">2.7</dbp:decLowC>
    <dbp:decLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">5.4</dbp:decLowC>
    <dbp:decMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7</dbp:decMeanC>
    <dbp:decPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">10.2</dbp:decPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:decPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">55.2</dbp:decPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:decRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">17.4</dbp:decRecordHighC>
    <dbp:decRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">-11.8</dbp:decRecordLowC>
    <dbp:decSun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">52</dbp:decSun>
    <dbp:direction rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">vertical</dbp:direction>
    <dbp:establishedDate rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">43</dbp:establishedDate>
    <dbp:establishedTitle rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Settled by Romans</dbp:establishedTitle>
    <dbp:febHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.9</dbp:febHighC>
    <dbp:febHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.4</dbp:febHighC>
    <dbp:febLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">4.7</dbp:febLowC>
    <dbp:febLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">2.1</dbp:febLowC>
    <dbp:febMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">6.8</dbp:febMeanC>
    <dbp:febPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.5</dbp:febPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:febPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">40.9</dbp:febPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:febRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">19.8</dbp:febRecordHighC>
    <dbp:febRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">-9.6</dbp:febRecordLowC>
    <dbp:febSun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">77.9</dbp:febSun>
    <dbp:float rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">left</dbp:float>
    <dbp:header rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Illustrated London Boroughs maps showing the percentage of races in each borough, according to the 2011 census</dbp:header>
    <dbp:headerAlign rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">center</dbp:headerAlign>
    <dbp:image rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">St James&#39;s Park Lake – East from the Blue Bridge - 2012-10-06.jpg</dbp:image>
    <dbp:image rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Aerial view of Hyde Park.jpg</dbp:image>
    <dbp:image rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">London Asian pc 2011.PNG</dbp:image>
    <dbp:image rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">London White pc 2011.PNG</dbp:image>
    <dbp:image rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">London Black pc 2011.PNG</dbp:image>
    <dbp:imageCaption rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Clockwise from top: City of London skyline, Trafalgar Square, London Eye, Tower Bridge and the London Underground roundel in front of Big Ben</dbp:imageCaption>
    <dbp:imageSkyline rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">File:London Montage L.jpg</dbp:imageSkyline>
    <dbp:janHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.5</dbp:janHighC>
    <dbp:janHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.1</dbp:janHighC>
    <dbp:janLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5</dbp:janLowC>
    <dbp:janLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">2.3</dbp:janLowC>
    <dbp:janMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">6.8</dbp:janMeanC>
    <dbp:janPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">11.1</dbp:janPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:janPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">55.2</dbp:janPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:janRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">17.2</dbp:janRecordHighC>
    <dbp:janRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">-13.2</dbp:janRecordLowC>
    <dbp:janSun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">61.5</dbp:janSun>
    <dbp:julHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">23.6</dbp:julHighC>
    <dbp:julHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">23.5</dbp:julHighC>
    <dbp:julLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">15.5</dbp:julLowC>
    <dbp:julLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">13.9</dbp:julLowC>
    <dbp:julMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">19.6</dbp:julMeanC>
    <dbp:julPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">7.7</dbp:julPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:julPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">44.5</dbp:julPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:julRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">36.7</dbp:julRecordHighC>
    <dbp:julRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">5.6</dbp:julRecordLowC>
    <dbp:julSun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">212</dbp:julSun>
    <dbp:junHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">21</dbp:junHighC>
    <dbp:junHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">22.4</dbp:junHighC>
    <dbp:junLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">14.1</dbp:junLowC>
    <dbp:junLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">11.7</dbp:junLowC>
    <dbp:junMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">18.3</dbp:junMeanC>
    <dbp:junPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.2</dbp:junPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:junPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">45.1</dbp:junPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:junRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">35.6</dbp:junRecordHighC>
    <dbp:junRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">1.5</dbp:junRecordLowC>
    <dbp:junSun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">204.3</dbp:junSun>
    <dbp:label rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Mixed</dbp:label>
    <dbp:label rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Asian</dbp:label>
    <dbp:label rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Black</dbp:label>
    <dbp:label rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Arab</dbp:label>
    <dbp:label rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Other</dbp:label>
    <dbp:label rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">White</dbp:label>
    <dbp:latd rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">51</dbp:latd>
    <dbp:latm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">30</dbp:latm>
    <dbp:latns rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">N</dbp:latns>
    <dbp:lats rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">26</dbp:lats>
    <dbp:left rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Religion</dbp:left>
    <dbp:location rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">London Weather Centre</dbp:location>
    <dbp:location rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">London Heathrow</dbp:location>
    <dbp:longd rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">0</dbp:longd>
    <dbp:longew rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">W</dbp:longew>
    <dbp:longm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7</dbp:longm>
    <dbp:longs rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">39</dbp:longs>
    <dbp:mapCaption rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Location of London in the United Kingdom</dbp:mapCaption>
    <dbp:marHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">11.3</dbp:marHighC>
    <dbp:marHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">11.7</dbp:marHighC>
    <dbp:marLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">5.8</dbp:marLowC>
    <dbp:marLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">3.9</dbp:marLowC>
    <dbp:marMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.8</dbp:marMeanC>
    <dbp:marPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">9.3</dbp:marPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:marPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">41.6</dbp:marPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:marRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">24.2</dbp:marRecordHighC>
    <dbp:marRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">-5.1</dbp:marRecordLowC>
    <dbp:marSun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">114.6</dbp:marSun>
    <dbp:mayHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">18.6</dbp:mayHighC>
    <dbp:mayHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">17.9</dbp:mayHighC>
    <dbp:mayLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">10.9</dbp:mayLowC>
    <dbp:mayLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.7</dbp:mayLowC>
    <dbp:mayMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">14.8</dbp:mayMeanC>
    <dbp:mayPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.8</dbp:mayPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:mayPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">49.4</dbp:mayPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:mayRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">32.8</dbp:mayRecordHighC>
    <dbp:mayRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">-0.9</dbp:mayRecordLowC>
    <dbp:maySun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">198.5</dbp:maySun>
    <dbp:metricFirst rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">yes</dbp:metricFirst>
    <dbp:novHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">11.1</dbp:novHighC>
    <dbp:novHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">11.9</dbp:novHighC>
    <dbp:novLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">4.9</dbp:novLowC>
    <dbp:novLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8</dbp:novLowC>
    <dbp:novMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">10</dbp:novMeanC>
    <dbp:novPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">10.3</dbp:novPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:novPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">59</dbp:novPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:novRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">20.8</dbp:novRecordHighC>
    <dbp:novRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">-7</dbp:novRecordLowC>
    <dbp:novSun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">72.6</dbp:novSun>
    <dbp:octHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">16.1</dbp:octHighC>
    <dbp:octHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">15.5</dbp:octHighC>
    <dbp:octLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.4</dbp:octLowC>
    <dbp:octLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">10.9</dbp:octLowC>
    <dbp:octMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">13.5</dbp:octMeanC>
    <dbp:octPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">10.8</dbp:octPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:octPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">68.5</dbp:octPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:octRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">29.9</dbp:octRecordHighC>
    <dbp:octRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">-3.3</dbp:octRecordLowC>
    <dbp:octSun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">116.5</dbp:octSun>
    <dbp:parts rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">&amp;</dbp:parts>
    <dbp:parts rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/City_of_London" />
    <dbp:parts rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">32</dbp:parts>
    <dbp:partsType rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Districts_of_England" />
    <dbp:populationAsOf rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2015</dbp:populationAsOf>
    <dbp:populationBlank rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">9787426</dbp:populationBlank>
    <dbp:populationBlank rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">13879757</dbp:populationBlank>
    <dbp:populationBlank1Title rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Greater_London_Built-up_Area" />
    <dbp:populationBlank2Title rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/London_metropolitan_area" />
    <dbp:populationDemonym rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Londoner</dbp:populationDemonym>
    <dbp:postalCodeType rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Postcodes_in_the_United_Kingdom" />
    <dbp:right rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">Percent</dbp:right>
    <dbp:seat rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/City_of_London" />
    <dbp:seat rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">&amp;</dbp:seat>
    <dbp:seat rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Greater_London" />
    <dbp:seatType rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Counties_of_England" />
    <dbp:sepHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">20.8</dbp:sepHighC>
    <dbp:sepHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">19.9</dbp:sepHighC>
    <dbp:sepLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">11.4</dbp:sepLowC>
    <dbp:sepLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">13.7</dbp:sepLowC>
    <dbp:sepMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">17.3</dbp:sepMeanC>
    <dbp:sepPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">8.1</dbp:sepPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:sepPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">49.1</dbp:sepPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:sepRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">35.4</dbp:sepRecordHighC>
    <dbp:sepRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">1.8</dbp:sepRecordLowC>
    <dbp:sepSun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">149.3</dbp:sepSun>
    <dbp:singleLine rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">yes</dbp:singleLine>
    <dbp:subdivisionType rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Countries_of_the_United_Kingdom" />
    <dbp:subdivisionType rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/List_of_sovereign_states" />
    <dbp:subdivisionType rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Regions_of_England" />
    <dbp:thumb rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">left</dbp:thumb>
    <dbp:title rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Outline_of_London" />
    <dbp:title rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Religion_in_London" />
    <dbp:titlebar rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#langString">#ddd</dbp:titlebar>
    <dbp:totalType rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Greater_London" />
    <dbp:unitPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://dbpedia.org/datatype/millimetre">1.0</dbp:unitPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:value rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">1.3</dbp:value>
    <dbp:value rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">59.8</dbp:value>
    <dbp:value rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">2.1</dbp:value>
    <dbp:value rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5</dbp:value>
    <dbp:value rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">18.4</dbp:value>
    <dbp:value rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">13.3</dbp:value>
    <dbp:width rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">250</dbp:width>
    <dbp:width rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">200</dbp:width>
    <dbp:yearHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">15.8</dbp:yearHighC>
    <dbp:yearHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">15.2</dbp:yearHighC>
    <dbp:yearLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">7.5</dbp:yearLowC>
    <dbp:yearLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">9.8</dbp:yearLowC>
    <dbp:yearMeanC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">12.8</dbp:yearMeanC>
    <dbp:yearPrecipitationDays rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">109.5</dbp:yearPrecipitationDays>
    <dbp:yearPrecipitationMm rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">601.7</dbp:yearPrecipitationMm>
    <dbp:yearRecordHighC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">38.1</dbp:yearRecordHighC>
    <dbp:yearRecordLowC rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">-13.2</dbp:yearRecordLowC>
    <dbp:yearSun rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double">1632.6</dbp:yearSun>
    <ns11:hypernym rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/resource/Capital" />
  </rdf:Description>
</rdf:RDF>